letslinkin.com 2009-05-01

# Letslinkin.com - Watch Videos

### Privacy Policy

**_Privacy Protection_**

This policy establishes how we handle the information we learn about you when you visit letslinkin.com (the "Website"). Protecting the privacy and personal data of our visitors is important to us, and we are committed to collecting, maintaining, and securing your personal information in strict accordance with the principles described in this policy.

Throughout this policy, the term "You" or "Your" refers to you, the visitor providing information to letslinkin.com. The term "We", "Our" or "Website" refers to this website, letslinkin.com. 

**_Collection of Information_**

In order to provide you with the highest level of service, we ask that you voluntarily provide us with certain information about yourself (collectively, your "Information"). Your Information includes, among other things, your name, your gender, your age, your physical location, your email address, and other information about yourself. Your Information may also include pictures and/or videos that your provide to the Website. Depending on how you participate at the Website, you also may be required to provide certain financial information to us.

**_Use of Information_**

Our privacy policy is simple: no one sees your Information unless (i) you want them to or, as described below, (ii) we have to share such information to comply with the law or to protect the Website.

We may disclose your Information if we are required to do so by law or we in good faith believe that such action is necessary to (1) comply with the law or with legal process; (2) protect and defend our rights and property; (3) protect against misuse or unauthorized use of our website; or (4) protect the personal safety or property of our users or the public (among other things, this means that if you provide false information or attempt to pose as someone else, information about you may be disclosed as part of any investigation into your actions).

In addition, we may use the information we obtain from our members in the aggregate (with all personally identifiable information removed) for promotional purposes, or to determine our members' demographics and preferences. By doing so, we are able to deliver targeted advertisements on our website which you may find to be helpful and informative. Also, in the unlikely event that the Website, or substantially all of the Website's assets are acquired, your Information may be one of the transferred assets.

Unless otherwise specified, we reserve the right to keep a copy of your Information indefinitely, and use such information in accordance with the terms of this Privacy Policy.

**_Maintenance or Revisions to Your Information_**

In order to make sure that you receive the full benefit of our website, you should make sure that we have the most up-to-date information about you. Please remember that we will not remind you to update your information, and it is your responsibility to make sure that we have your correct information.

As a registered member, you can revise your information at any time. 

**_Internet Privacy_**

In order to provide better service, we will occasionally use a "cookie." A cookie is a small amount of data which our website stores on your computer, and which we can later retrieve. The cookie cannot be read by a site other than ours. We use cookies for a number of administrative purposes; for example, to store your preferences for certain kinds of information. No cookie will contain information that will allow anyone to contact you via telephone, e-mail, or any other means. You can monitor our use of cookies on your computer by setting your Web browser to inform you when cookies are set, or you can prevent the cookies from being set entirely. The "help" portion of the toolbar on most browsers will tell you how to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, how to have the browser notify you when you receive a new cookie, or how to disable cookies altogether. Please understand that if you disable the use of cookies on your computer, you may be unable to access certain portions or services of our website.

The Website also may use third parties to display advertisements and track leads and/or sales from our website. These ads and/or tracking functions may use cookies. The Website does not control these cookies, and they are not subject to the Website's privacy policy.

**_Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA)_**

The Website is directed to the general public. The Website does not knowingly offer services or information to children, nor does the Website knowingly request information from children. If you are under 18, you may not use the Website under any circumstances. We reserve the right to cancel, without prior notice to you, any services or access requested by you if we know, or have reason to believe, you are not over the age of 18.

**_Changes to Our Privacy Policy_**

As our members' needs change, we may find it necessary to amend or revise this policy. Any revisions or additions to this policy will be posted on this page. Please re-visit this page from time to time to make sure that you are aware of any additions or revisions to this policy. If you have any concern about privacy at the Website, please send a thorough description of your concerns to [legal@letslinkin.com](mailto:legal@letslinkin.com) and we will try to resolve them. This policy may change, and use of information that we gather is subject to the privacy policy in effect at the time of collection or use of the information.

**_Electronic Notification_**

When you sign up with the Website, you consent to receive any privacy or other notices, agreements, disclosures, reports, documents, communications, or other records (collectively, "Notices") from the Website electronically. You consent to receive Notices electronically in either or both of the following ways: 

  1. We may post the Notice on our website (www.letslinkin.com); or 

  2. We may transmit the Notice to you by email, using the email address you provide to us. 

All Notices provided to you electronically will be deemed to be "in writing." 

**_Your Options_**

You can always choose not to provide us with your Information, even though it might be needed in order to begin or continue your registration or membership with the Website. When you update information in the manner described above, we usually keep a copy of the prior information for our records.

Should you choose not to accept the terms outlined in this privacy policy (or any revised version of this policy), you may withdraw as a member from our Website. To Withdraw, you must contact us at [admin@letslinkin.com](mailto:admin@letslinkin.com) and provide us with your full name, screen name, and email address. If you withdraw as a Website member, the Website may retain the Information we have collected up to the date of your withdrawal, and use that Information as described in this policy.

As described above, we sometimes collect anonymous information from visits to our site to help

**_Security_**

We intend to protect the quality and integrity of Your Information. The Website has implemented technologies and security policies to protect the stored personal data of our users from unauthorized access, improper use, alteration, unlawful or accidental destruction and accidental loss. We will continue to enhance our security procedures, as new technology becomes available. letslinkin.com employees and processors who have access to personal data are obliged to respect the privacy of our visitors and the confidentiality of their personal data.

**_Links_**

Throughout the Website you will find links to third party sites. Please note that if you click on any of these third party links, you will be re-directed away from letslinkin.com. The Website is not responsible for the privacy policies or content on third party sites. You should be aware that when you visit or use services at third party sites, your data may be collected by those sites.

**_Privacy Support_**

If you have any inquiries about our privacy policy, please contact us at [admin@letslinkin.com](mailto:admin@letslinkin.com).  
  
## Copyright (c) 2007-2008 Letslinkin.com - Watch Videos. All Rights Reserved.   
Powered By: [Letslinkin Videos](http://www.letslinkin.com/)
